muzaini.com 2017-11-21

# Al Muzaini :: Always near you

Many visitors are worried about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This validates the need for this Privacy Policy to address those concerns. Al Muzaini EXCHANGE is strongly committed to protecting the user’s privacy.

Personal information means information that can be linked to a specific individual, such as name, address, telephone number and e-mail address. We encourage the user to review our Privacy Policy, and become familiar with it, but the user should know that we do not sell or rent our users' personal information to third parties. We don’t require you to register or provide this information to us in order to view our site or have access to its content.

####  Collection of Information

At our site, we collect both personal information and aggregate information that the user voluntarily provides either while on the site or in response to emails in relation to features provided on the site. Personal information relates to an individual consumer - e.g., name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, demographic information etc. We don’t require you to register or provide this information to us in order to view our site or have access to its content...

Aggregate information relates to such things as how many consumers visit the site, which pages they access, what information they download, the type of web browser and operating system you use, the name of your Internet Service Provider and so on. When you visit our site, we automatically collect this information, and combine it with similar information collected about all other visitors. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors.

The user can visit our website without revealing the user’s identity or any personal information. We track the Internet address of the domains from which people visit us and analyse this data for trends and statistics, but the individual user remains anonymous.

For better management of the site, we may (i) log the user’s browsing history; (ii) log non-personally-identifiable information, including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type; and (iii) record User IP addresses for security and monitoring purposes.

####  Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of the user’s computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it will enable us to relate the user’s use of this site to information that the user has specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information that the user supplies. A cookie cannot read data off the user’s hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We may use cookies to track user traffic patterns. Our advertising system may deliver a cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

The user can refuse cookies by turning them off in the browser options. If the user has set the browser to warn the user before accepting cookies, the user will receive the warning message with each cookie. The user need not have turned the cookies on to use this site.

####  Member Communications and Email

We employ a strict policy against sending unsolicited email. Please note that opting not to receive email does not exempt the user from receiving administrative emails.

Our Customer Care department may contact the customer in response to the customer’s inquiries, to provide services at the customer’s request and to manage the customer requirement.

Our website and email may contain links to various other sites. While we make every effort to ensure that our advertisers post clear and complete Privacy Policies and observe appropriate data practices, each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of ours. The privacy practices of other websites and companies are not covered by this policy.

####  Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect the user’s personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We reserve the right to disclose the user’s personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our site.

####  Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that we review our Privacy Policy from time to time, and we may make periodic changes to the policy in connection with that review. Therefore, the user may wish to bookmark this page and/or periodically review this page to make sure the user has the latest version.

####  Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:

**Al Muzaini Exchange**  
PO Box 2156 SAFAT 13022  
Al Mubarakiya  
Kuwait City  
kuwait

Tel.: +965 - 1888818

We’ll be happy to resolve your concerns
